<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Citra on Citra </title>
    <link>http://localhost:3000/</link>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <author>Citra</author>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2017, Citra; all rights reserved.</rights>
    <updated>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 03:01:10 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citra Progress Report - 2017 June</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2017-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 12:38:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <author>anodium</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2017-june/</guid>
      <description>The summer of 2017 has just rolled in, and although we don&amp;rsquo;t have a summer of code, the patches continue rolling in regardless. We&amp;rsquo;ve got a ton of fixes this month in the renderer, so this report is going to be very screenshot heavy. With that out of the way, let&amp;rsquo;s get right to it. Implemented Procedural Texture (Texture Unit 3) by wwylele There is a rarely used feature in the 3DS&amp;rsquo; GPU called procedural textures, &amp;ldquo;proctex&amp;rdquo; for short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citra Now Has A Game Compatibility Wiki!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/compatibility-list-wiki-created/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 11:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>saphiresurf</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/compatibility-list-wiki-created/</guid>
      <description>As game compatibility has broadened and the popularity of Citra has risen there&amp;rsquo;s always been a lack of consistent information on what could be played in Citra and what couldn&amp;rsquo;t. Often times the best way to find out if a game was working properly in Citra was to jump in and test it for yourself, but if any issues were encountered you&amp;rsquo;d be left scouring through forums sifting through potentially out of date information for answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citra Progress Report - 2017 P1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2017-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 23:20:00 EDT</pubDate>
      <author>anodium</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2017-p1/</guid>
      <description>In the last quarter, we&amp;rsquo;ve further improved the speed and accuracy of citra along with supporting more 3DS features, and we are very excited to show what we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit hard to believe, but Citra is already three years old, and in these three years we&amp;rsquo;ve gone from an emulator that could barely run homebrew, to one that can run many commercially available games at playable speeds!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Moving to Discourse!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/were-moving-to-discourse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 20:36:00 EST</pubDate>
      <author>flamesage</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/were-moving-to-discourse/</guid>
      <description>As we approach the first birthday of Citra&amp;rsquo;s website, we&amp;rsquo;d like to announce yet another project infrastructure update:
We&amp;rsquo;ve decided to launch a new forum based on the Discourse forum software!
When we first introduced the new website back in February of 2016, we chose to use Flarum over more classic forums used on other websites (such as phpBB, MyBB, or vBulletin). The reason for this was because Flarum was a much more modern platform, with better mobile support, and a attractive and innovative UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Nightly Builds are back!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/the-nightly-builds-are-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <author>leo121</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/the-nightly-builds-are-back/</guid>
      <description>As you all know, the Nightly builds have been down for some time now due to the former maintainer not being around, but the issues have been resolved, and the Nightly builds are now available on our downloads page once again! With downloads available for Windows, macOS, and Linux, you&amp;rsquo;re no longer required to compile the build yourself.
Likewise, we&amp;rsquo;d like to remind all users that any bugs found within Citra, or during emulation, be reported from the Nightly builds, and not the Bleeding Edge ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate Your Savefiles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/migrate-your-savefiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 16:56:00 EST</pubDate>
      <author>thekoopakingdom</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/migrate-your-savefiles/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: You do NOT need to follow this guide if you downloaded Citra for the first time after December 6th, 2016 OR if you have freshly installed Citra since using an older build.
In new versions of Citra, the location of saves has changed, so this guide will show how to migrate your saves to the new location on Window (Linux and macOS Bleeding Edge builds are planned, we are currently busy working on bringing nightly builds back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Bleeding Edge Builds</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/announcing-bleeding-edge-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 14:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jmc47</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/announcing-bleeding-edge-builds/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s hard to wait. We&amp;rsquo;ve noticed that users are very excited about the future of Citra, which means wanting to try all of the changes all of the time. But, emulator development can be a slow, arduous process as new changes can bring big regressions and problems with the much wanted new features.
In order to satiate the needs of our users, we&amp;rsquo;ll be adding new builds for download: bleeding edge builds!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We now have a Discord server!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/we-now-have-a-discord-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 15:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>thekoopakingdom</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/we-now-have-a-discord-server/</guid>
      <description>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of Discord yet, it&amp;rsquo;s basically an alternative to Skype, featuring servers with both voice and text chat. You can use it in your browser, download the desktop program, or get the mobile app.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have an account already, you can make one for free here.
Once you&amp;rsquo;ve done that, you can join Citra&amp;rsquo;s official server by going here.
There are 5 channels:
 #read-first - A read-only introduction to the server, and announcements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HLE Audio Comes to Citra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/hle-audio-comes-to-citra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 18:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>merrymage</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/hle-audio-comes-to-citra/</guid>
      <description>Special thanks must be given to fincs and the rest of the 3DS community for their work reverse-engineering the DSP firmware. Without that work, Citra would not be this far with audio emulation.
As of May 19th, 2016, Citra now has preliminary High Level Emulation (HLE) audio support! This means that users playing on Citra no longer have to listen to the deafening sound of silence in many titles. To get to this point was a huge reverse-engineering effort done by multiple people, with much of the reverse-engineering and the final implementation for Citra coming from MerryMage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texture Forwarding brings HD output to Citra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/texture-forwarding-brings-hd-output-to-citra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 21:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jmc47</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/texture-forwarding-brings-hd-output-to-citra/</guid>
      <description>One of the big things everyone has been wondering about Citra is when it will be able to render games at HD resolutions. One of the great things about emulators is that they can surpass the limitations of the original console, especially when it comes to graphical fidelity. With the 3DS specifically, many beautifully detailed games are hidden behind staggeringly low resolution screens topping out at 400x240. With Texture Forwarding (from tfarley, based on yuriks early implementation), Citra can now output games at any resolution, and runs faster as well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citra Progress Report - 2016 P1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2016-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 12:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>jmc47</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2016-p1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first Citra Progress Report of 2016! While 2015 will be considered the year that Citra first played games, 2016 is quickly shaping up as a year filled with higher compatibility, greater stability and much more as Citra matures. The avalanche of new features from tons of contributors has made it hard to keep up with everything even for developers!
Because there have been so many changes and there are so many different games, it can be very hard to keep up with what is working and what is not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citra Progress Report - 2015 P2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2015-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 15:30:00 EST</pubDate>
      <author>bunnei</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2015-p2/</guid>
      <description>This month we bring you the second installment of our two-part progress report on Citra in 2015! With this part, we discuss the evolution from Citra being able to barely run a few commercial games at a few frames-per-second, to where it is in 2016: Running many retail games at reasonable speeds, some of which are fully playable with near flawless graphics! We discuss Citra&amp;rsquo;s new &amp;ldquo;dyncom&amp;rdquo; CPU core, the OpenGL renderer, per-pixel lighting, and various bug fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citra Progress Report - 2015 P1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2015-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 23:30:00 EST</pubDate>
      <author>bunnei</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/citra-progress-report-2015-p1/</guid>
      <description>While Citra was first founded in April of 2014, visible progress for the emulator didn&amp;rsquo;t really happen until the turn of the year. After a long struggle to get anything to boot, 2015 saw Citra evolve from an experimental emulator that couldn&amp;rsquo;t run games into an experimental emulator that can run games. And while it may not seem like Citra is that far along, it is truly amazing how much things have progressed in just a year since the first commercial title booted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the New Citra!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:3000/entry/welcome-to-the-new-citra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 22:18:00 EST</pubDate>
      <author>flamesage</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:3000/entry/welcome-to-the-new-citra/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the brand new Citra website! This new site has been a sort of secret project off and on for over a year now. A lot of hard work, a few false starts, but here we are! This has been a big team effort - we&amp;rsquo;d like to especially thank Flame Sage, the primary architect behind the new website backend; MaJoR for the design and artwork, and lastly jchadwick for his early on role in the project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
